Justin Mc Nary

Web Developer

justinmcnary.com

justinmcnary34@gmail.com 480-276-2671 Charlotte, North Carolina

https://github.com/justinmcnary

www.linkedin.com/in/justin-mc-nary-a4201210b

Skills

Development

Advanced: JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, Responsive mobile-first design, Git, GitHub, NPM, REST APIs, FlexBox.

Proficient: React, MongoDB, SCSS, TDD with Jasmine, webpack and ES6.

Design

Advanced: Ilustrator, Photoshop.

Expert: Written & verbal communication, project management, social media marketing, decision making.

Education

THINKFUL

Web Development Intensive Program.

Six-month course on modern full stack JavaScript development.

Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards by collaborating several hours every week with a senior web developer.

Summary



Front-end developer skilled in writing, clean, testable code. Experienced with React, jQuery, Node, vanilla JavaScript, and mobile-first responsive development with HTML5 and CSS3. Familiar with modern tooling, frameworks, and ready to pick up the right tools for the job.

Experience

Operating Partner

2015-2017

Schwag Apparel, San Diego, CA

through initial hiring and product creation; oversaw the operation of day to day tasks, training of departments, and pushing sales. Managed a team of talented designers and print artists, created and edited original artwork for customers. Began studying web development to expand business opportunities. Eventually through partnerships and an optimized online presence I was able to step away from daily operations and focus on development full time.

Responsible for company organization and structuring



General Manager

2012-2015

The Double Deuce, San Diego, CA

Responsible for all aspects of the high volume hospitality venue. Including but not limited to hiring, training, scheduling appropriate staff for bar, promotional, and security positions. Controlled purchases and inventory, negotiated prices and contracts, developed preferred suppliers, reviewed and evaluated usage reports, analyzing variances, and taking corrective actions. Established business plan by surveying demand; conferring with people in the community; identifying and evaluating competitors; preparing financial, marketing, and sales projections, analyses, and estimates. Maintained efficient operations by implementing policies and standard operating procedures, implementing production, productivity, quality, and patron-service standards, determining and implementing system improvements.

a

Bar Manager

2011-2012

The Tipsy Crow, San Diego, CA

Created a new and unique beverage program for the venue. Devised weekly promotions both in store and online. Managed Social Media marketing. Dealt with daily staffing needs, negotiated product sales and managed monetary tasks. After 6 months was promoted to General Manager at sister venue The Double Deuce.